https://www.mobridgetribune.com/privacy-policy/

Search for:
Privacy Policy
The privacy of our website’s visitors is important to us.
This Privacy Policy explains what information may be collected through your use of our website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party products or services for which a separate privacy policy is provided.
Your use of our website constitutes an agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
I. What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Purpose of Information Collection
We collect information to help us analyze our users’ interest in our content, allowing us to make better decisions about the type of content we provide. We also may use the information we collect for marketing purposes.
Third-Party Analytics and Advertiser Services
Like most websites, we may employ third-party analytics and advertiser services, such as those of Google Analytics, AdSense, and Matomo, on our website. These third party services use technologies such as cookies, web beacons, web server logs and similar technologies to collect information. The information collected is of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited throughout our site.
The information collected may be disclosed to these third parties, who use the information, for example, to evaluate use of the website. The third parties may also use the information for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Here is more information on how Google uses data.
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non-personally identifiable information.” It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
If you fill in a form on our site you may opt-in to saving your name and email address on our site.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
II. How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
III. Your control over information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at anytime by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
You can opt out of all Google Analytics tracking software – click here to download their browser opt-out add-on. You can also opt out of DoubleClick.
IV. Additional information
How we protect your data
Our data is secured against cross site access and passwords are securely stored with a one way secure method.
What data breach procedures we have in place
In an event of a data breach, the site in question would be locked down and if reader information is accessed, we will notify the affected users and reset their passwords.
What third parties we receive data from
None
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
None
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
We have no industry regulatory disclosure requirements.
Privacy Policy Changes
The Privacy Policy may be changed at our sole discretion. We encourage our visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Trending Stories1WATCH LIVE: 2020 Mobridge Snow Queen PageantFree Access2Beau DuBray was excellent student and athlete3Principal Gerald Labbe dies4Two Hearts making progress5Outside the Fence: Soon there will be no turning back
By continuing to browse or by clicking 'Accept', you agree to our sites privacy policy.AcceptPrivacy policy
